AD.MC.028
AbuDhabi
College de la Sainte Famille Collection
1880-1990
AD.MC.028
AbuDhabi
4.0 Paige boxes
Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt
Object AD_MC_028
Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Religion; Schools/Education
- School portrait with young boys. 12.4 x 16.7 cm, Circa 1900; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Classrooms; Fezes/Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students
- School portrait with teachers including Catholic priests. 11.6 x 18 cm, 1903; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref2)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Ceremony; Classrooms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religion; Religious Clothing; Religious Crosses; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Three children in the Japanese Gardens. 13.3 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref3)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Costumes; Family Portraits; French Writing; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Maritime/Nautical Outfits; Photographic Prints
- Eva laurella in her car. 8.3 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref4)
  Arabic Writing; Cars; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Women
- Eva Laurella's car, a Fiat 508B Balilla. 8 x 11 cm, Circa 1934-1937; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref5)
  Arabic Writing; Cars; Helwan, Egypt; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Women
- Group portrait of school staff with friar Modesto. 11.5 cm x 17.6 cm, Circa 1915; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref6)
  Arabic Writing; Beards; Fezes/Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Medals; Mustaches; Photographic Prints; Religion; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Tables; Teachers; Ties; Uniforms
- Students on a field trip to the White Desert (Farafra). 14.4 cm x 9.3 cm, 1951; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref7)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Deserts; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Shorts; Students; Trips
- Students on a field trip with Father Varatto. 8.6 cm x 13.7 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref8)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Deserts; Field-trip; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Rocks; Schools/Education; Shorts; Students
- Boys' gymnastics class with Father Rodrigo. 9.1 cm x 13.8 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref9)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Belts; Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Shorts; Sports; Students; Trees; Windows
- School portrait of students and Father Giacomelli. 12.7 x 17.8 cm, Circa 1900; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref10)
  Arabic Writing; Beards; Belts; Boys; Children; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- School portrait. 14.3 x 11.1 cm, Circa 1900; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref11)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Shoes/Boots; Students
- Boys' gymnastics class in the school courtyard held by Father Rodrigo. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref12)
  Arabic Writing; Belts; Boys; Children; Column/Colonnade; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Shorts; Sports; Students
- Two nuns with students at the beach in Alexandria, Egypt. 9 x 9.9 cm, Circa 1940-1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref13)
  Alexandria, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Beaches; Boys; Children; Girls; Group Portraits; Italian Writing; Nuns; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Shorts; Students
- Boys' gymnastics class with Father Rodrigo. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref14)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Column/Colonnade; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Shorts; Sports; Students; Windows
- Boys carrying watermelons in Wallis Resort, Suez. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref15)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Fruits & Vegetables; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Italian Writing; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Shorts; Suez, Egypt; Watermelons
- Men photographed by Laurella at Evergreen Hotel. 6.4 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref16)
  Arabic Writing; Cameras; Fezes/Tarbouches; Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Hotels; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Uniforms; Windows
- Laurella's car (a Fiat Balilla) on the road close to the pyramids. 6 x 8.6 cm, Circa 1934; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref17)
  Arabic Writing; Cars; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Women
- School trip to the pyramids. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref18)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Field-trip; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Pyramids; Pyramids of Giza; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Shorts
- Four boys posing in theatrical costumes with guns in the school theater. 12.3 x 17 cm, Circa 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref19)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Column/Colonnade; Costumes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Guns; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Painted Backdrops; Performance Plays; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Theater
- Four boys posing in theatrical costumes in the school theater. 12.3 x 17.3 cm, Circa 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref20)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Canes/Walking Sticks; Children; Column/Colonnade; Costumes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Painted Backdrops; Performance Plays; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Theater; Wigs
- School dormitory. 12.4 x 16.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref21)
  Arabic Writing; Beds; Buildings; Dormitories; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Windows
- Two trucks parked on 55 Moustafa Fahmi Street. 12.9 x 12.8 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref22)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Buildings; Cars; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Italian Writing; Palm trees; Schools/Education; Streets/Roads; Trucks; Windows
- School portrait with young boys and four teachers in gardens. 13.1 x 18 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref23)
  Boys; Children; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Grass; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Palm trees; Parks; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Trees
- Group portrait of the school staff in a garden with Father Milan. 11.8 x 18 cm, 1930; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref24)
  Arabic Writing; Beards; Fezes/Tarbouches; Flowers; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Teachers; Turban; Uniforms
- King Fuad I of Egypt signing an official document in Helwan. 17.8 x 13.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref25)
  Arabic Writing; Ceremony; Documents; Fezes/Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; King Fuad I of Egypt; Medals; Military/Soldiers; Officials; Pens & Inkwells; Photographic Prints; Stamps; Uniforms
- Children sitting at a table outside and peeling vegetables. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref26)
  Arabic Writing; Bicycles; Boys; Children; Cutlery; Food; Fruits & Vegetables; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Suez, Egypt
- Helwan Wax Museum exhibit of a man reciting from the Qur'an. 12.6 x 8.9 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref27)
  Arabic Writing; Exhibitions; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Museums; Photographic Prints; Quran/Koran; Religious Clothing; Sculpture
- King Fuad I of Egypt in front of the Physical Department of the Meteorological Station. 17.9 x 13.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref28)
  Arabic Writing; Canes/Walking Sticks; Fezes/Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; King Fuad I of Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Procession; Uniforms
- Group portrait with Father Cremono at Suez Canal in front of a boat. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref29)
  Arabic Writing; Boats/Ships; Boys; Canals; Children; Docks/Piers/Jetties; Flags; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Rivers; Suez, Egypt
- A group of boys standing by the Colossus of King Ramses II in Memphis, Egypt. Taken by Father Cremono. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref30)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Memphis, Egypt; Museums; Photographic Prints; Ramses II; Sculpture; Statues; Students
- Man sitting at Wadi Hof in the Helwan desert. 12.3 x 9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref31)
  Arabic Writing; Canes/Walking Sticks; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Landscapes; Men; Photographic Prints; Traditional Dress; Wadi Hof, Helwan, Egypt
- Photograph of a Scout Leader; Sabry with Father Aletto in the palm area. 8.9 x 13.6 cm, 1949-1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref32)
  Arabic Writing; Canes/Walking Sticks; Fezes/Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Scouts; Shorts; Uniforms
- Men and Women dining at Evergreen Hotel. 7 x 10.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref33)
  Arabic Writing; Bottles; Chairs; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Fezes/Tarbouches; Food; Gatherings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Hotels; Italian Writing; Meals; Men; Photographic Prints; Plates; Tables; Ties; Uniforms; Waiters; Women
- Students on a field trip to Fayoum, posing in front of a bus. 9.2 x 14.4 cm, 1955; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref34)
  Arabic Writing; Beards; Belts; Boys; Buses; Children; Fayoum, Egypt; Field-trip; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Schools/Education; Streets/Roads; Students; Teachers
- Three children sitting with Doctor Ghanz outside on 26 Sherif Street. 13.9 x 9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref35)
  Arabic Writing; Children; Doctors; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Shoes/Boots; Streets/Roads; Trees
- Group portrait of boys at Suez Resort, two hold fishing nets. 13 x 13.1 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref36)
  Arabic Writing; Children; Fences; Fishing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Pottery; Shorts; Suez, Egypt
- Boys sitting around a dining table in Suez. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref37)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Classrooms; Eating; Field-trip; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Meals; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Suez, Egypt; Tables
- Street view of 39 Heidar Pacha Street. 10.7 x 13.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref38)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Entrance; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Trees; Windows
- Villa and garden of Dr. Ghanz on 26 Sherif Street. 12.9 x 12.9 cm, Undated.; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref39)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Cactus; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Italian Writing; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Trees; Window Blinds; Windows
- Helwan school banner. 13.8 x 9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref40)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Ceremony; Flags; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Insignia/Emblem; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education
- Students on a boat with professor Martini on the Nile. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref41)
  Arabic Writing; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Boats/Ships; Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Nile River; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Rivers; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- A man wearing a uniform standing on the shore of the Suez canal. 13.9 x 9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref42)
  Arabic Writing; Canes/Walking Sticks; Coast; Fezes/Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Police; Suez, Egypt; Uniforms
- Students on a field trip standing with Father Cremono. 9.3 x 14.4 cm, 1952; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref43)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Bridges; Children; Field-trip; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Rivers; Schools/Education; Shorts; Students; Teachers
- School portrait with a priest. 9 x 12.1 cm, Circa 1895; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref44)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Maritime/Nautical Outfits; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students
- Students and teachers posing on top of a tower in Suez. 14.2 x 9.3 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref45)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Buildings; Children; Field-trip; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Towers
- The Caude Refractor at the Helwan Observatory. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1902; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref46)
  Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Observatory; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Telescope
- Teachers and students in paddle boats. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref47)
  Arabic Writing; Boats/Ships; Boys; Children; Field-trip; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Lakes; Men; Photographic Prints; Pond; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- School dormitory. 9 x 14 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref48)
  Arabic Writing; Beds; Dormitories; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Interiors; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education
- Students posing in the desert during a school field trip. 14.5 x 9.7 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref49)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Deserts; Field-trip; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Shorts; Students
- Students at the Japanese Garden. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref50)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Field-trip; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Sculpture; Students; Teachers
- Buddha statues in the Japanese Garden. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref51)
  Arabic Writing; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Pond; Sculpture; Statues; Water
- Father Cremono with men next to palm trees. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref52)
  Animals; Arabic Writing; Camels; Deserts; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Traditional Dress; Turban
- A shepherdess posing in front of goats during a field trip to Helwan El-Balad. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1952; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref53)
  Animals; Arabic Writing; Boys; Canes/Walking Sticks; Countryside/Rural; Field-trip; Gelatin Silver Prints; Goats; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Shepherds; Traditional Dress; Women
- Students during a school trip on a felucca. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref54)
  Arabic Writing; Boats/Ships; Boys; Children; Field-trip; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Nile River; Photographic Prints; Rivers; Sails; Schools/Education; Students; Water
- Group portrait of boy scouts. 14 x 6.4 cm, 1980; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref55)
  Arabic Writing; Banners; Boys; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Scouts; Students; Teachers; Uniforms
- Eva Laurella posing on a horse with another woman. 10.2 x 8.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref56)
  Animals; Arabic Writing; Dresses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Horses; Men; Photographic Prints; Traditional Dress; Women
- Postcard of Muhammed Tewfik Pasha I. 13.8 X 9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref57)
  Arabic Writing; Fezes/Tarbouches; Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Italian Writing; Men; Officials; Ottoman; Pasha; Photographic Prints; Postcards; Royalty; Uniforms
- Postcard of Khedive Isma'il Pasha. 13.9 x 9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref58)
  Arabic Writing; Fezes/Tarbouches; Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Italian Writing; Men; Officials; Ottoman; Pasha; Photographic Prints; Postcards; Royalty
- Students in a classroom taken by Father Cremono. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref59)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Classrooms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students
- Students acting in a school play. 9.3 x 12.8 cm, 1954; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref60)
  Acting; Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Costumes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Performance Plays; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Theater
- Alumni in costume at school theatre. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref61)
  Acting; Actors; Arabic Writing; Costumes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helmets; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Painted Backdrops; Performance Plays; Photographic Prints; School alumni; Shields; Spears; Theater; Uniforms
- Restaurant of the Evergreen Hotel. 8.6 x 13.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref62)
  Arabic Writing; Chairs; Fezes/Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Hotels; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Tables; Windows
- Students performing in a play. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref63)
  Acting; Actors; Arabic Writing; Boys; Chairs; Costumes; Curtains; Fezes/Tarbouches; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Performance Plays; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Sets; Students; Theater
- Students and man in costume for school play. 9.3 x 12.1 cm, 1954; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref64)
  Acting; Actors; Arabic Writing; Beards; Boys; Children; Costumes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Theater
- Giordino Giopponese. Group posing in the Japanese Garden. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref65)
  Arabic Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Jewelry; Men; Photographic Prints; Shoes/Boots; Statues; Ties; Women
- Student playing the trumpet with Father Aletto. 13.8 x 9 cm, 1949-1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref66)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Brass Instruments; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Students
- Group portrait of school staff. 9 x 13.2 cm, 1962-1963; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref67)
  Arabic Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Moustaches; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Teachers; Ties; Women
- Students at a sports event playing tug of war. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Circa 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref68)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Buildings; Children; Competition; Crowds; Flags; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Ropes; Schools/Education; Spectators; Sports; Sports Kit/Sportswear; Sports teams; Students
- Two buses on the road for a school field trip to Fayoum, Egypt. 8.6 x 13.5 cm, 1955; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref69)